{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622911","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622911","name":"El Taco Veloz #1","address":"6170 Toledo","zipcode":"48209","owner":"Hector M. Hernandez","licenseNumber":"236352","licenseType":"Mobile Food Establishment","establishmentType":"LHD - Mobile Food Establishmen","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.10985,42.31903","geojson":{"id":"51622911","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.109854275,42.319034393]},"properties":{"name":"El Taco Veloz #1","owner":"Hector M. Hernandez","address":"6170 Toledo","zipcode":"48209","license_type":"Mobile Food Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"236352","establishmentid":"51622911","establishment_type":"LHD - Mobile Food Establishmen","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4342","name":"El Taco Veloz","address":"6170  Toledo","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4613","name":"El Taco Veloz #1","address":"6170 Toledo","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4668","name":"El Taco Veloz #2","address":"6170 Toledo","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51622920","name":"El Taco Veloz #3","address":"6170 Toledo","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3143","name":"Tacos El Taquito Mexican Food","address":"1985 Military","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"931","name":"Neinas Elementary","address":"6021 McMillan","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1052","name":"Blue Diamond","address":"2453 Campbell St. N.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51623062","name":"Wing Stop","address":"6166 Vernor Hwy","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"5104","name":"Bella's Coffee House ","address":"2303 Campbell St.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4240","name":"Mega Tortas","address":"6237 Federal","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"59778","inspectionDate":"2022-07-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Mobile Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-08-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"5-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Receptacles and waste handling units for REFUSE, recyclables, and returnables used with materials containing FOOD residue and used outside the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be designed and constructed to have tight-fitting lids, doors, or covers.\n(B) Receptacles and waste handling units for REFUSE and recyclables such as an on-site compactor shall be installed so that accumulation of debris and insect and rodent attraction and harborage are minimized and effective cleaning is facilitated around and, if the unit is not installed flush with the base pad, under the unit.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With doors,lids or covers","subProblem":"Not provided","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"TRASH CAN","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-501.111","violationDescription":"Storage areas, enclosures, and receptacles for REFUSE, recyclables, and returnable's shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Receptacle(s)","subItem":"waste","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"TRASH CAN","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"56820","inspectionDate":"2021-12-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Mobile Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"HOT WATER","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-01-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand-drying towels","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-01-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"54830","inspectionDate":"2021-05-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Dispensing utensil","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."}]},{"inspectionid":"53120","inspectionDate":"2020-10-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"52500","inspectionDate":"2020-08-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Openings","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Discard"}]},{"inspectionid":"48390","inspectionDate":"2019-07-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand-drying towels","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-07-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"degreaser","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Chemicals (spray type)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-07-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"shelves","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Shelf","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"45468","inspectionDate":"2019-03-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"HOT WATER","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"Thermometer(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622911"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}